#### **Contact Information**

#### **Email**

aartiahireengit@gmail.com

#### **Address**

Mumbai

## **Phone**

+919767944070

#### **Skills**

React JS

Redux

CSS

**React Hooks** 

Vue Js

**Typescript** 

**Javascript** 

Core Java

Data Structure

## Languages

## **English**

Advanced

#### Hindi

Advanced

### Marathi

**Native** 

## Sanskrit

Intermediate

## **Aarti Ahire**

## Senior Software Engineer

Currently working as front end developer in the technology React.Js, Vue.Js, Javascript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS and having the demonstrated history of working in the information technology with overall 4.7 years of experience and 4 years in front end domain. I am looking for new opportunities and challenges where I can fully use my skills for the success of the Organization.



#### Experience

Belfast, UK May 2023 - Present

## **Front End Developer**

#### **Funds Axis**

Worked on highwire project as front end developer to develop sections in form of table with dropdowns to fields, integration of API, centralized store implementation for getting api data, updating and deleting etc using vue.js and javascript for front end. Interacting with BA and QA to gathering requirement, analysis it and suggesting changes for improvement of project, Writing manual test cases and end to end test cases for the project. Worked on Opal project using react.js and typescript to

implement the template using word addin, document creation, helping backend developer to understands the issues of the project is from API or from front end and resolving it.

## Noida Aug 2020 - Apr 2023

## **Senior Software Engineer**

### **Magic EdTech**

Achievements/Tasks Designed interactive user interface using Vue.Js, typescript and have good ability to translate designs and wire-frames into high-quality code. Used React.Js, HTML, CSS, Javascript in development of web applications, created unit test cases for the application. Work with different stakeholders within and outside the team in a highly collaborative environment. Achieved timely and flawless deliveries by applying best practices in development and Followed SDLC in Agile Development Model. Guided junior peers as required to achieve overall targets as a team. Active participation in scrum ceremonies to generate clear picture of end to end business needs and edge cases through requirement gathering discussions.

## Mumbai Feb 2020 - Aug 2020

## **Fellowship Engineer**

## **BridgeLabz Solutions**

Achievements/Tasks Single-handedly developed Bookstore, Notes Front-end using React.Js, HTML and CSS, media - query and used conditional rendering in designing of application Created projects like 'Employee Wage, Flip Coin Simulator, Snake Ladder' and Tic Tac Toe using Shell Scripting and logicimproving programs in Java Followed best coding practices to maintain quality of code Learn problem solving abilities and good knowledge of Data Structures

## Chantilly, USA Jun 2019 - Feb 2020

## **Talent Acquisition Associate**

## **Ampcus Inc**

Achievements/Tasks Worked as a talent acquisition associate to find talented IT engineers for various positions in IT industries of the USA

## **Education**

Nashik, India Jun 2016 - May 2019

- **Bachelor of Information Technology** Nashik District Maratha Vidya Prasarak Samaj's
- Thakare College of Engineering

**Diploma in Computer Technology** K.K Wagh with Distinction

# Jun 2013 - May 2016

**Achievements** 

Nashik, India

Project selected in NES innovation Awards, Paper published in Internatinal Journal for Technological Research in Engineering(IJTRE) on "IT ENabled Farming", State Level Project Presentation First Prize (2018 - 2019)